{
  "Questions": [
    {
      "question": "(Category: 1) What does HTML stand for?",
      "choice1": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "choice2": "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
      "choice3": "Home Tool Markup Language",
      "choice4": "High Text Markup Language",
      "answer": 1,
      "answerData": "Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage?",
      "choice1": "Head, Title, HTML",
      "choice2": "Title, Head, HTML",
      "choice3": "HTML, Head, Title",
      "choice4": "Head , HTML, Title",
      "answer": 3,
      "answerData": "HTML, Head, Title"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct HTML for adding a background color?",
      "choice1": "Body style=''background color: yellow''",
      "choice2": "background=''yellow''",
      "choice3": "Background yellow /backgroundBody ",
      "choice4": "color=''yellow''",
      "answer": 2,
      "answerData": "background=''yellow''"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following tags contains metadata about the webpage?",
      "choice1": "<head>",
      "choice2": "<title>",
      "choice3": "<body>",
      "choice4": "<main>",
      "answer": 1,
      "answerData": "head"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you add a paragraph in html?",
      "choice1": "<paragraph>",
      "choice2": "<a>",
      "choice3": "<img>",
      "choice4": "<p>",
      "answer": 4,
      "answerData": "p"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following selector selects  elements that are checked?",
      "choice1": "E ~ F",
      "choice2": "::after",
      "choice3": ":checked",
      "choice4": "none of them",
      "answer": 3,
      "answerData": ":checked"
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML is what type of programming?",
      "choice1": "Macro programming",
      "choice2": "Markup language",
      "choice3": "Scripting language",
      "choice4": "Programming language",
      "answer": 2,
      "answerData": "Markup language"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the proper way to add a page break?",
      "choice1": "<break add>",
      "choice2": "add <break>",
      "choice3": "<br>",
      "choice4": "/break",
      "answer": 3,
      "answerData": "br"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following  selects  the target of a referring URI?",
      "choice1": ":URLselect",
      "choice2": ":target",
      "choice3": ":URI",
      "choice4": ":select",
      "answer": 2,
      "answerData": ":target"
    },
    {
      "question": "The attribute of <form> tag is?",
      "choice1": "Method",
      "choice2": "Action",
      "choice3": "Both",
      "choice4": "None of them",
      "answer": 3,
      "answerData": "Both"
    },
    {
      "question": "Markup tags tell the web browser about?",
      "choice1": "How to organise the page",
      "choice2": "How to display the page",
      "choice3": "How to display message box on page",
      "choice4": "None of them",
      "answer": 2,
      "answerData": "How to display the page"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Category: 2) <p> 20 </p> What will this tag display on browser? (click next button to enter your answer)",
      "choice1": "",
      "choice2": "",
      "choice3": "",
      "choice4": "",
      "answer": "",
      "answerData": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "____ is the correct HTML tag for the largest heading? (click next button to enter your answer)",
      "choice1": "",
      "choice2": "",
      "choice3": "",
      "choice4": "",
      "answer": "",
      "answerData": "h1"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Category: 3) HTML tags are case sensitive",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "choice3": "-",
      "choice4": "-",
      "answer": 2,
      "answerData": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "All web pages should have an <html>, <head>, and a <body> element.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "choice3": "-",
      "choice4": "-",
      "answer": 1,
      "answerData": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a tag with attributes: <p class='info'>",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "choice3": "-",
      "choice4": "-",
      "answer": 1,
      "answerData": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Elements are the same as tags.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "choice3": "-",
      "choice4": "-",
      "answer": 2,
      "answerData": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Category: 4) <p id='Quiz'></p> What will this tag display on browser?",
      "choice1": "It will display nothing",
      "choice2": "Quiz",
      "choice3": "Paragraph",
      "choice4": "None of them",
      "answer": 1,
      "answerData": "It will display nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "<p id='Quiz'>Hello!!</p> What will this tag display on browser?",
      "choice1": "It will display nothing",
      "choice2": "Paragraph",
      "choice3": "Quiz",
      "choice4": "Hello!!",
      "answer": 4,
      "answerData": "Hello!!"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Category: 5) The ______ attribute tells the browser which HTML page to load.",
      "choice1": "link",
      "choice2": "href",
      "choice3": "src",
      "choice4": "load",
      "answer": 3,
      "answerData": "src"
    }
  ]
}
